browneyedbaker.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Brown Eyed Baker

### PRIVACY POLICY LANGUAGE

Below is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applicable to your use of BrownEyedBaker.com (the “Web Site”). The Privacy Policy affects your rights as an individual user, as well as the rights of Brown Eyed Baker, LLC (“Brown Eyed Baker”).

Brown Eyed Baker is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This Privacy Policy tells you about the information we collect on our Web Site, what we do with that information, and with whom we share the information. In order to ensure your privacy, information Brown Eyed Baker collects from visitors to its Web Site is used only in the manner and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. By using the Web Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy, which may be modified from time to time.

### Information Collected

The information gathered falls into two categories: (1) information you supply when you register to receive emails or comment on the Web Site, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through the Web Site.

### Personally Identifying Information

In operating the Web Site, Brown Eyed Baker may utilize registration, comment forms, online surveys, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, addresses, e-mail addresses, and/or telephone numbers (“Personal Information”).

### Agreement to Collect, Use and Disclose Personal Information

Your provision of Personal Information to Brown Eyed Baker and/or this Web Site means that you agree that we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these terms, you should not provide any Personal Information. Unfortunately, certain services can only be offered if you provide Personal Information to us. Consequently, if you choose not to provide us with any required Personal Information, we may not be able to offer you those services.

### Tracking Information

 **Cookies**. From time to time, the Web Site may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications, which feature stores on your computer a small piece of data about your visit to our Web Site. The Web Site does not set any Personal Information in cookies, nor does it employ any data-capture mechanisms on the Web Site other than cookies. Cookies shed light on which areas of the Web Site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Web Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

 **Click Tracking**. As is true of most websites, Brown Eyed Baker gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the Web Site, track users’ movements around the Web Site and gather demographic information about the user base as a whole. Except as noted herein, this automatically-collected data is not linked to Personal Information.

 **IP Addresses**. Each user’s IP address is logged with each visit and each action performed on the Web Site. This information is never provided to third parties, except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, and is logged only for a temporary period of time. IP address information is linked to Personal Information and may be used in an effort to block a “banned” user from accessing the Web Site.

 **Advertising**. Brown Eyed Baker uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information (not including your Personal Information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Participation on a Public Website**. You should be aware that any Personal Information you submit to the comments section of the Web Site may be read, collected, or used by other users of this Web Site, including anonymous visitors.

### Cookie Opt Out

You can opt out of cookies using the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out at this page:  
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

You can also choose to disable or selectively turn off cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.

### How Your Information Will Be Used

 **Personal Information**. Your Personal Information will not be shared with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. Your Personal Information may be used to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Web Site. Your contact information may also be used to inform you of any changes to the Web Site, or to send you additional information about Brown Eyed Baker. Brown Eyed Baker does not sell, trade, barter or exchange for consideration any Personal Information it has obtained.

 **Anonymous Information**. Anonymous information is used to analyze Web Site traffic, but this information is not examined for individually identifying information. In addition, anonymous IP addresses may be used to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

 **Use of Cookies**. Cookies may be used to deliver content specific to your interests. Promotions or advertisements displayed on the Web Site may contain cookies. Brown Eyed Baker does not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on the Web Site.

 **Disclosure of Personal Information**. Unless permitted by law, no Personal Information is collected about an individual without first obtaining the consent of the individual to the collection, use and dissemination of that information. Consent may be written, verbal or implied as necessary to further your needs. Personal Information will be collected, to the extent possible, directly from the individual concerned. Personal Information may be disclosed if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on the Web Site, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Brown Eyed Baker or the users of this Web Site, or (3) act under circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of this Web Site. When obliged to do so, Brown Eyed Baker will not disclose more information than is required.

### Security

Brown Eyed Baker has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that is obtained from you, but there are no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse or alteration to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

### Personal Information of Minors

If you are under the age of eighteen (18), you may use this Web Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Brown Eyed Baker is committed to protecting the privacy of children. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect Personal Information online from children under the age of 18.

### Comments

Brown Eyed Baker may include interactive forms such as comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

### Third Party Websites

Brown Eyed Baker may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, Brown Eyed Baker is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

### Disputes

If you choose to access, visit, browse, shop on or otherwise use this Web Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and this Web Site’s Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania. If you have any concern about privacy at this Web Site, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

### Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Web Site, without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web Site. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

### Site Policies, Modification, and Severability

Please review our other policies, such as our Terms and Conditions of Use, posted on this Web Site. These policies also govern your use of this Web Site.

### Contact

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or practices related to this Web Site, please contact michelle@browneyedbaker.com.

This policy was last updated on August 24, 2010
